CONTACT

SARVESH SADGURU GAWDE

- @ gawadesarveshh@gmail.com
- 7040206467 / 8766509830
- H. No.9, Shashi Sadan, Near Laxmi Petrol Pump, Mundvel, Vasco-Da-Gama, Goa.



OBJECTIVE

A self learning individual having an enthusiasm to complete particular given task or work on time. Time bounded and Punctual person, not ready to sacrifice on time for a particular project. Having an amazing environmental background with few months of experience and also making things proper on site as well as in office.

EXPERIENCE

2 March 2021 - 23 March 2021 Dilip BuildCon Limited.(New Zuari Bridge, Cortalim, Goa)

Trainee

Undergone Training on Construction of Cable Stayed Bridge including approaches across River Zuari on NH-17/NH-66.

11 October 2021 - 14 May 2022 Sanofi India Ltd.

Assistant HSE Officer

Working as an HSE Officer and In charge of ETP. Also, inspecting and ensuring safety against various works going on site (Civil, Mechanical, Electrical). Being from Civil Engineering field, I rather check all the construction norms/procedures being followed on overall site.

EDUCATION

August 2021

Goa College Of Engineering, Farmagudi, Ponda-Goa

B.E.Civil Engineering

71.35 %

March 2017

• St. Andrews Higher Secondary School, Vasco-Da-Gama, Goa.

HSSC (Science)

71.1%

March 2015

• Mother Of Mercy English High School, Merces-Vaddem, Goa.

SSC

73%

SKILLS

- Team Work
- Problem Solving
- Enthusiasm towards Learning new concepts.
- Good Understanding of Softwares.

PROJECTS

Case Study On New Mandovi Bridge(Atal Setu).

Neccesity of New Mandovi Bridge and Interaction Effects of Foundation of New Mandovi Bridge with existing bridges and its Maintainance.

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

- Student Member, Indian Concrete Institute. (November 2019 October 2019)
- In Recognition for participating in Third Dr. Victor de Mello Goa Lecture and ISSMGE TC-107 symposium on Laterites and Lateritic soils. (20th September 2019 - 21th September 2019)
- In recognition for participating in Seminars organised by Asian Civil Engineering Council. (27th September 2019)
- In recognition for achieving 85% in online quiz on RCC Design organised by Department of Civil Engineering, Singhad Academy of Engineering, Kondhwa, Pune. (25th May 2020 - 28th May 2020)
- In recognition for participating in webinar on "Hydration and Microstructure Properties of Nanosilica Admixed Cementitious Mortar." organised by Goa College of Engineering, Farmagudi, Ponda-Goa. (01st June 2020)
- In recognition for participating in the webinar "Compaction and Consolidation-Theory and Practical Applications" organised by Goa College of Engineering, Farmagudi, Ponda-Goa. (03rd June 2020)
- In recognition for participating in webinar "Structural Health Monitoring using Peizo Sensors" organised by Goa College of Engineering, Farmagudi, Ponda-Goa. (05th June 2020)
- In recognition for successfully completing in locating epicentre and determining magnitude of a virtual earthquake. (24th March 2021)

INTERESTS

- Exploring Hidden Places
- Cricket
- Food Explorer
- · Learning Civil Engineering related Softwares

LANGUAGES

• English, Hindi, Marathi, Konkani.

REFERENCE

- Dr. Purnanand Savoikar "Goa College Of Engineering, Farmagudi, Ponda Goa"
 Professor in Civil Engineering
 psavoikar@gmail.com
 8322336314
- Ashish Kamat "Priority Constructions"
 Manager- Projects
 7447498024
- Sandeep Prabhu "Sanofi India Ltd."
 Associate Director of Engineering
 9011029546